# NIAMAT MARJAN

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **ABOUT ME**

Innovative Front-End Developer and UI/UX Designer with a passion for creating engaging digital experiences. Equipped with a keen eye for detail and a deep understanding of user-centered design principles, I bring creativity and technical expertise to every project.

mniamatmarjan@gmail.com



#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelors Degree in Computer Science

Jan 2021 - Present

- Informatics Institute of Technology
- Colombo, Sri Lanka

#### **Advanced Level**

Sept 2018 - Jun 2020

- Royal Institute
- Colombo, Sri Lanka

#### SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3
- ReactJs, NextJs
- Javascript / Typescript
- Java
- Python
- Figma
- Google Analytics, SEO
- MongoDB, ORM, CMS
- Git, GitHub

#### **REFERENCES**

#### Nirmal Fernando

Associate Director/Architect WSO2 LLC nirmal@wso2.com | +94 71 5779733

#### Thishani Charles

Associate Technical Lead WSO2 LLC thishani@wso2.com | +94 77 2556931

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# WSO2 LLC (Pvt) Ltd.

Software Engineer Intern

Jul 2022 - Jul 2023

Colombo, Sri Lanka

Having worked on various React projects, contributed to API development using WSO2 Integration Studio and WSO2 Micro Integrator, and participated in several Java projects.

 Technology Stack Used: ReactJs, Java, Maven, Swagger API, Ballerina, MaterialUI, Google Analytics

### ZRI Adventures (Pvt) Ltd.

Web Developer

Colombo, Sri Lanka Aug 2023 - Present

Designed and developed the company website (www.zriadventures.com) and is currently an active maintainer

- Technology Stack Used: Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Strapi CMS, Google Analytics and Cloudinary Integration
- Client is hosted on vercel and Server was hosted in Railway

#### **Dunes Cart**

Web Developer

Dubai, United Arab Emirates Mar 2024 - Present

Currently developing the company website and is an active maintainer

- Technology Stack Used: Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Strapi CMS, Google Analytics and Cloudinary Integration
- · Client and database is hosted on vercel